A City Held In The Grip Of Fear. One Man Fearless Enough To Stop It.
Open Fire is a action film directed by Kurt Anderson.
Mercenaries leads from Kruger seize an entire city,
and one man sets out to stop them.
Alec Mcneil, played by Jeff Wincott.
Lynne Tolbert, played by Mimi Craven.
Kruger, played by Patrick Kilpatrick.
Bob McNeil, played by Lee de Broux.
Special Agent Davis, played by Arthur Taxier.
Walter the Guard, played by Bert Remsen.
Open Fire is single British television crime drama film, made for
ITV, which first broadcast on 12 November 1994.
The film was written and directed by Paul Greengrass, and concerns the police manhunt for David Martin, who escaped from custody
following his arrest for shooting a police officer, leading up to the shooting in error of another man, Stephen Waldorf.
The film starred Rupert Graves as Martin, as well as Samuel West as Waldorf, Douglas Hodge
as investigating officer DC Peter Finch, and Kate Hardie as Sue Stephens.
Open Fire was filmed in Belsize Park and in around Hampstead, London.
The film has never been released commercially.
The UK based TV Channel Talking Pictures TV has since
shown Open Fire, firstly on 5 October 2024.